

PROFILE

I offer 4 years of experience in development, currently working as a Software Engineer in Coventry UK.

The ultimate goal is to keep growing my career specifically as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Programming is my passion, I am highly motivated, focused, with a lot of will to keep learning.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+44 7448719858

EMAIL:

atanasskambitovv@amail.com

LINKS

GitHub:

https://github.com/NASOKILA

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanas-kambitov-a69528162/

LANGUAGES

English | Italian | Spanish | Bulgarian

DIPLOMAS & CERTIFICATES

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates

ATANAS KAMBITOV

Software Engineer

EDUCATION

South-West University "Neofit Rilski" 15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 (4 years) Bachelor degree in Informatics.

Private Software University (SoftUni)

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Professionally graduated and qualified C# and JavaScript developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sainsbury's Store Support Centre | Software Engineer | Coventry UK 03/12/2018 – Now (7 months)

Design, build and test multiple continuous integration systems.

Working in an agile team of five people using GitHub, Jira and DevOps.

Provide scalability, availability and performance following solid principles.

Setup a .Net Core based server architecture with a React.js client side.

SoftUni | Junior Web Developer | Sofia, Bulgaria

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Create, host and maintain backend API's, databases and frontend apps. Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines in a high pressure work environment with deferent technologies, languages and frameworks.

Paolo Pavia | Prestashop & WordPress Developer | Sofia, Bulgaria

11/02/2015 – 19/05/2016 (1 year and 3 months)

Develop, support and refactor cloud based applications related to shopping, advertisement and promotion.

Successfully increase sales and client traffic on our applications by 130%.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Agile Methodologies | Azure DevOps | Kubernetes | GitHub | Docker Microservices | REST API | .NET Core | .Net Framework | React.js | SQL Redux | Angular.js 2+ | Typescript | Vue.js | JavaScript | Mongo DB HTML5 & CSS3 | JQuery | Less & Sass | Bootstrap | Node.js & Express

PERSONAL PROJECTS

.Net Core

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

Angular.js 2+

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop/ https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

React.js

https://nasokila.github.io/house-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/house-shop